now I know your scope he's like being
horizontal let's go be alright alright
guys so this is this drive is to
determine whether we will be awarding
energy behind a Bosch bounty or not know
what it might be
[Laughter]
we can always baby ever try to always
maybe here we are driving in our on
their awkward
aarrr 2.0 litre awkward yeah
so we're using a petal procedure wait
well he's fine yeah you have to restart
after he stopped yeah yes oh really can
we spend the button well yeah so the
public yes I want to do it before
emerging yeah the public we spamming the
button is that so if you press it so if
you press it multiple times then you can
increase the speed and so you have to
press it when they go in stop this
you're gonna be seeing I'll stop okay I
start to bother why don't you guys see
yourself instead of dealing with
adership
what am I here how is how is Ottawa why
do we do it the way we don't do it our
ourself instead of letting other people
doing it why don't we do what deport Wow
well the bounty program was we're
winding down the bounty program but it
was a nice way to just pay some money
yeah I mean we don't have what the cops
do right so we didn't have this car
before and the 90% of the cut was done
it's great like especially for these
people to maintain the car afterward
yeah if we want to bring in some of
these cars make an official we were I
have said we're only doing Honda's in
Toyotas officially everything else we're
gonna kind of we change up the back
carbon whole now we're gonna do James
officially jail yeah so Honda's Toyota's
and GM's
so like right now I just engaged like
that shouldn't be allowed I shouldn't be
allowed to engage it stopped about well
so disease unfortunately we don't know
like we can't detect it because it's
deceased like we don't know if there are
objects change that I just made
necessary like before I wasn't allowing
the system to engage even behind the car
because we talked there were no objects
but that's there enough yet yeah so I
changed it but I'm surprised that the
actual system allows you to engage
yeah me too yeah sure well to be fair
you're stopped so even if you release
the brake it's not gonna move to Allah
brake
well that's fine remove right yeah
because we're in stopped yeah well is
there a race like what if I see that's
weird
yeah it's it took so long to say stopped
yeah like I was a race condition well I
mean whatever special stage all right so
carbon tax
anybody should just go there straight to
stop stay in transitional place guys you
know I'm excited for tomorrow I can see
all of it on the heads-up display here
too which is pretty cool yeah um it's
okay if it's like the I think it's like
the C because X era yeah
does it have it has Honda user we don't
do the special user stuff like we do
internal NGM no no yes I tried it it's
like accelerating it also seems to steer
down to a lower speed not much power
it's not I think it's lower as far as
the below 5 kph it sends out the state
that I didn't see before
step 3 and maybe it's day three even
four massive torque
oh cool state mad and but that's like 5
kph right that's much better
but I'm not sure so I like that just
engage on gas for it wouldn't do that
the video exactly scope is what were
there fantastic
like that like the Honda for good I feel
very safe with
that's nice I cool
hey guys it's looking pretty good so far
we'll do our standard Allu yeah put test
against Iran deal on maybe they're
protesting against people trying to make
housing affordable cheap housing
overpriced what do you think of
Microsoft blankie table neutral on it I
know I don't have much ill will toward
Microsoft um I mean like you can say
like Windows was bad but like no in 2001
it wasn't it was the best thing to use
right we use Azure okay about it
um I hope they don't like try to
Microsoft to fire too much but
what could make it get home better off
they put good search back in but search
to begin is too much it wasn't like
seven points I simplified to my steel
man mr. macho you get for you
finally becoming a million dollars yes
ping-pong anger why does the boss just
is also sending this this ping-pong is
pretty bad
well it was like a bit offensive because
that's the Bosch system not us the
wobble is yeah well I mean it's like it
was like shadow not shadow
yeah mounted there with the rearview
mirror removed or lovely we can't
officially tell you to remove every
mirrors but that's the lovely Aeon
placement right there
like Africa is back up camera now
you want to see me no idea just use a
side mirror yeah
I just take up they take up valuable
window real estate if it could be spent
on screens
there's a ping-pong game just bad like
that 45 has been highway 10
no I think it was but see well you know
what I don't like we can't get anything
about the what okay so I just looked at
that I freaked out for a minute I'm what
you're talking see the car doesn't see
the car yeah I see that's the problem
wait but it must see the car cuz how we
doing that clipping
well that's vision base yeah I think
it's a vision but you see the problem
right but it makes it more this is
pretty good I'll say it's not vision how
are we getting the distance to that car
energy energies online how are you well
you're doing it somehow do you see oh
mercy it's just luck with our speed yes
[Music]
okay I don't like that I mean I don't
like not being able to see that heads up
[Music]
I'm gonna try my best to hack the radar
guys I have something else to work on
you're gonna love it it's gonna be great
but we had some great things planned for
you guys no very very exciting things
not just new models but new models will
happen too
I really like this that's not just
binder yes yeah yeah you can send it I
said it on there as copies can see it
but like there is a display
but we display the much rather stuff for
this no because that violates the
purpose right
but we couldn't we at least get one bit
of information about whether there's
meat all right yeah yeah we do me after
that I did that
where's that turn so bad and what no I
think maybe we don't then why did it
and is it going - max - ours is a tuning
finger no like a tuning is the same as
the Civic and it's like the city is it
the same event yeah
I really felt as the center
that victim was less on the highway
I didn't feel like it's a lot this is
not supercruise quality not even close
oh come on don't get that ping-pong okay
so it does torque yeah
wait it's a steering temporarily
unavailable what no but just because you
all be riding is that what do you want
oh okay okay that's interesting yeah
yeah
not before it doesn't beep when you over
I just keep it a warning when you hear
the beep
the torque is crappy yeah I think we got
why am i why am I Oh guys you you didn't
do it in experience the GM torque yeah
the GM has torque it has low latency
there's only two by Cadillac ct-6 s and
then you'll use super cruise to be like
not by the end of the year you'll be
like wow
don't you wish Jim can update super
cruise energies right that this is half
of the target that we use in our city we
have lead Civic Torquemada lead Civic
Torquemada
the posh ACCC is good yep
much better than the other yeah
when do you expect to be better than
Superboy's end of the year and to the
Year Bowl so we're gonna roll it I'm
gonna roll out our maps before then so
I'm gonna be better than supercruise in
the highway everybody is the same but
he's not the same affic strategy
right-hander required
you don't think we have time oh well
Vasquez knows this right now yes I mean
[Music]
therefore power check it out
we've maps be free absolutely
as in beer or lunch or whatever they're
good for us I don't think we're going to
quite do dedication at the public domain
I think we're gonna have an attribution
clause but other than that we'll be
completely the super gross tight to take
a seat
I've seen it disengage for exits but no
it never tries to take it's all based on
the map like the curvature of the road
is to turn to driving happens to seams I
mean it seems to me requires at least
the one lane line
we've looked at the lanes you can look
at the laser just on the canvas so we've
looked at the output from the mobile eye
quality oh yeah so yeah there was a
lookout steer fix yeah just don't send
us the well no don't send this steer
enable beat to zero when a steer command
is actually zero anybody found found a
bug that was affecting these cars yeah
well this gets us what so this is the
Accord what else these guesses the
kohrville the new CRV and over the third
car was a tough car and you helped me
out so I call the CRV 5g and oh the H
back yeah so we're gonna we're gonna
make we're gonna make an official comma
Bosch giraffe oh yeah I'm gonna add an
Ethernet connector we're gonna add a
comma power connector to it
girls are for sale eventually
[Music]
yeah we needed you're awfully job we did
power because these castles in the right
power constantly to advise
I see ping-pong here is it is it a model
park or well let's see I need to see oh
wow yeah likewise but you shouldn't do
that
Subaru's doesn't own a transaction
you don't like that it doesn't fit I
just use the car this is the car better
job well I'm having a really bad GM ACC
breaking events I got the gossiping
strong ones you got goes bringing GM
with this one missed yeah yeah yeah I
got a couple of the other strong one Wow
pretty good something yeah
I guess
maybe we should try to figure out how to
work my torque into the UI
how to somehow like they that did where
the talk is being applied yeah
yeah
yeah we I think I think we are we are
spoiled to by just how much better in
our Civic us yeah
[Music]
as your team able to compete with large
companies like Tesla it's just your own
Talent
Tesla's my child people - it has think
about how a Pikachu competes with an
Onix
quick attacks agility
a lot more probably slips through the
cracks of Tesla - and a lot more kind of
kind of crap anyone complained about in
this last letter we don't uh real tight
graphic over
yeah I mean we also have laws to do
right like we're not building your car
oh the stock wait so we're just
forwarding the lane detect as well but
we're doing our own oh no no that's
foger that's ours or well the lanes I
think we are sending our sure that there
are different packets yes it should be
their stuff it's being proxy by unser
it's actually there can message because
look the lane departure warning is
working out there in departure warning
yes it's working top of top of that
what's the top of this okay well that's
cool
I think it's a different message
but yeah they need about your work so
this really needs more torque like the
Toyota has no problems here
what's a replay everybody do we know the
Italians card it's the same one Oh
what's the exact same Minister justice
ever yes okay and it smells a melon ah I
like the steel here is a little
different it's definitely not the same
but exotic same as zero this one sells
like a different status that could be a
tuning um like the Acura and the Civic
have completely different steering
program they don't share a single line
of code they made by a different company
[Music]
really does not like standardization
which I don't understand well energy
says it's defined what its different
steering state module
I really have to do a third back so wait
you're saying that like the Aqua and the
city done share knows you deserve it's a
completely different processor
completely different manufacturer
they just kept the same API yeah
it's gonna be our demo car for the cross
yeah he doesn't even think it's the same
well it might be one of
this he might be back there I mean we
can't read it we can't use this is a
press deck my car
one better yes wait I I almost like ours
breaking to a stop more than me breaking
to a stop yeah no I wonder one of those
days like we went out with like the
newest MPC change just like wow oh
that's actually good the same sort of
right message well I don't know that
this car
can open vitals work with the Tesla the
old Tesla yeah there is a fourth kind of
working on it but we're never gonna
support that main line yeah we don't we
don't compete with Tesla it's it's kind
of like think about an Android port for
iOS yes one was done and maintained by a
few people but in reality you're on iOS
under I'm sorry I never record for idle
so that's why
it's getting that lightweight over there
it's like hard it really like switches
yeah I think that's a you're really
getting a couple foot change to them yes
well the new one thing is old I know
what
the new model is trained using all the
same stuff that we use to make our maps
so if it's mapping quality it's
certainly model quality
like all the lanes just come from the
same plant extract abuse of maps
what's the verdict so far can tell if
the complains means it's bad news oh you
get about me I know it's not good it's
on par with some of the other cars I
just generally Drive about how open tile
it should be better but I think I would
have a lot of these same complaints if
we went grab the Civic and disabled
some of them are specific like not
saying I mean the biggest complaint I
haven't really is not saying weaker and
breaking being kind of crappy and my
biggest complaint is the torque guys I'm
who can I contribute to that bounty for
hacking the torque terrible yeah it
sucks that it's dangerous guys oh you
wanna see dangerous oil you see the GM
do we post we show the scope is like the
real Jam torque yeah so the GM message
God should we tell them this they might
no one has that car okay we're good so
you can send the message from zero to
150 and that's like the Lane Keeping
Assist and that's like similar torque to
what's in the Toyota but then if you set
the supercruise bit you can send up to
300 300 torques is a lot of Tours yeah I
never seen it even in the angle control
for the angle interface parking he was
focused on oh yeah I was like bouncing
at the end of like you showed me that it
was unbelievably strong
I don't know I mean do you think GM have
you ever seen to go above 150 I don't
know I never seen going above 150 but
never supers I never see anything didn't
like I looked at to long routes and I
never seen it going about 250 so I would
not be surprised if they have the same
safety we do yeah
all right they're just like well we're
gonna put it in the thing Oxford mean
aunt Cass it's like if you send 150th
high speed it's gonna flip out so you
know Cassie definitely has like
different safety yeah that's super gross
I was very hard to work with that gas on
the Cadillac we can use that's fine
alright guys so yeah we're gonna
upstream this at the end of sprint so uh
ten days Tom will pay out the bounty
energy if your watch off half the value
right now I'm eternity merchant or
internal code base
congratulations you have the second car
big bounty Claire not that big it's too
good that's a respectable $2,000 oh yeah
nice job we'll get this out and that's
it and that ends the car bounty program
we're actually on there's still one
bounty available Toyota Camry
if anybody can do the Toyota Camry this
is still a bounty available for you um
you do why should we do lateral only
only Cameron Kelly was it you don't
lateral only on the Camry pretty easily
right well I think so yes because well
but people if you do some proxy where do
we attack so well it's no that's fine
it's fine we should be able to do like
lateral and easily matter only but but
boxing is probably our first camera yeah
dress supports that I think maybe it's
kind of going with the radar
Robert Lee slaughter should be able to
no problem yeah I don't know sense the
lateral control but I'm pretty sure
it'll be the camera yeah yeah we're kind
of okay with shipping some lateral onlys
what we're going try to make loans you
did another one on these guys that's
alright
if its lateral only it will still ship
look at them rocking out depends by on a
bike with big headphones on cool alright
alright skull piece when will we start
selling boss giraffes we make them open
either puppies gonna come sooner maybe
after the tokens
[Laughter]